[{"questionBody":"IsSystem_Security :belongs_to :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :System_Security :belongs_to :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :System_Security :belongs_to :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :System_Security :belongs_to :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsActive_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"Is :standard_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :standard_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :standard_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :standard_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsHybrid :extension_of :Tree ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Tree"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Tree"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Tree"},{"questionBody":"IsHybrid :extension_of :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsHybrid :extension_of :Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsHybrid :extension_of :Mesh ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Mesh"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Mesh"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hybrid :extension_of :Mesh"},{"questionBody":"IsPhysical :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Physical :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsBOOTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsBOOTP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BOOTP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsBASET :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASET :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsActive_Hub :kind_of :Hub ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :kind_of :Hub"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"questionBody":"IsFinger_protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Finger_protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Finger_protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Finger_protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Application ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Application"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Application"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Application"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Data_Link ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Data_Link"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Data_Link"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Data_Link"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Presentation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Presentation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Presentation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Presentation"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Network"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :is_a :ISO_Standard ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :is_a :ISO_Standard"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :is_a :ISO_Standard"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :is_a :ISO_Standard"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Transport ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Transport"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Transport"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Transport"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :deployed_in :Computer_Networks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Physical ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Physical"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Physical"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Physical"},{"questionBody":"IsOSI_Model :contains :Session ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Session"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Session"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OSI_Model :contains :Session"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Hybrid ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Hybrid"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Hybrid"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Hybrid"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Dairy_Chairs ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Dairy_Chairs"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Dairy_Chairs"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Dairy_Chairs"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Point_to_Point ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Point_to_Point"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Point_to_Point"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Point_to_Point"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Tree ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Tree"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Tree"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Tree"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Mesh ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Mesh"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Mesh"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Mesh"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Bus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Bus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Bus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Bus"},{"questionBody":"IsTopology :classify_as :Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Topology :classify_as :Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsAdvance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsAdvance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Advance_Direct_Connect :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsHigh_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :High_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :High_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :High_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"questionBody":"IsPacket_Switching :approaches :Switched ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Switching :approaches :Switched"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet_Switching :approaches :Switched"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Switching :approaches :Switched"},{"questionBody":"Is_ac :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_ac :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_ac :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_ac :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsBASETX :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASETX :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASETX :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASETX :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsBASET :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASET :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsRDP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RDP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RDP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RDP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsSilicon_Photo_Diode :uses :Silicon_Photo_Diode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Silicon_Photo_Diode :uses :Silicon_Photo_Diode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Silicon_Photo_Diode :uses :Silicon_Photo_Diode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Silicon_Photo_Diode :uses :Silicon_Photo_Diode"},{"questionBody":"IsThroughput :improve :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Throughput :improve :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Throughput :improve :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Throughput :improve :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Exploits ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Exploits"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Exploits"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Exploits"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Worm ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Worm"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Worm"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Worm"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Downloaders ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Downloaders"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Downloaders"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Downloaders"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Root_Kit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Root_Kit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Root_Kit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Root_Kit"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Logic_Bomb ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Logic_Bomb"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Logic_Bomb"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Logic_Bomb"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Flooders ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Flooders"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Flooders"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Flooders"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Spammer_Programs ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Spammer_Programs"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Spammer_Programs"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Spammer_Programs"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Backdoor ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Backdoor"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Backdoor"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Backdoor"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Auto_Rooter ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Auto_Rooter"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Auto_Rooter"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Auto_Rooter"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Key_Loggers ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Key_Loggers"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Key_Loggers"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Key_Loggers"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Zombie ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Zombie"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Zombie"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Zombie"},{"questionBody":"IsMalicious_Software :contains :Torjan_Horse ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Torjan_Horse"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Torjan_Horse"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Malicious_Software :contains :Torjan_Horse"},{"questionBody":"IsOFDMA :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OFDMA :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :OFDMA :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :OFDMA :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsDistribution_Switch :kind_of :Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :kind_of :Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distribution_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsSNMP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsSNMP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsPOP2 :version_of :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP2 :version_of :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :POP2 :version_of :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP2 :version_of :POP"},{"questionBody":"IsStar_Ring :extension_of :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsStar_Ring :extension_of :Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Ring :extension_of :Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsStream_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stream_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Stream_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stream_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_2003 :version_of :Windows_Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2003 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_2003 :version_of :Windows_Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2003 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"questionBody":"IsWireless :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsProduction_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Production_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Production_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Production_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"},{"questionBody":"IsNovel_Netware :kind_of Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Novel_Netware :kind_of Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Novel_Netware :kind_of Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Novel_Netware :kind_of Server"},{"questionBody":"IsInterception :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interception :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Interception :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interception :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsPassive_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Passive_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Passive_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Passive_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsDirect_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Direct_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Direct_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Direct_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsCircuit_Switching :approaches :Switched ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Switching :approaches :Switched"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Circuit_Switching :approaches :Switched"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Switching :approaches :Switched"},{"questionBody":"IsUser_Datagram_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :User_Datagram_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :User_Datagram_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :User_Datagram_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsSOAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SOAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SOAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SOAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsDSSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DSSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DSSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DSSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"questionBody":"IsDSSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DSSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DSSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DSSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsApple_Share :approaches :Peer_to_Peer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Apple_Share :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Apple_Share :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Apple_Share :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"},{"questionBody":"IsRTSP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsRTSP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RTSP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsFram_Relay :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Fram_Relay :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fram_Relay :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Fram_Relay :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"IsSingle_Mode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Single_Mode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Single_Mode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Single_Mode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsDirect_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Direct_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Direct_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Direct_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"},{"questionBody":"IsError_Rate :utilize :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Rate :utilize :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Error_Rate :utilize :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Error_Rate :utilize :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsLow_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Low_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Low_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Low_Interaction_Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"questionBody":"IsYahoo :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Yahoo :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Yahoo :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Yahoo :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :utilize :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :utilize :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Multiport_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Source_Route_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :classify_as :Transparent_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"IsBridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bridge :belongs_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsPHP :offers :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PHP :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :PHP :offers :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PHP :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsTranslation :functions :Presentation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Translation :functions :Presentation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Translation :functions :Presentation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Translation :functions :Presentation"},{"questionBody":"IsCat6 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat6 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cat6 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat6 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"questionBody":"IsWiretapping :perfoms :Passive_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wiretapping :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wiretapping :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wiretapping :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsPOP1 :version_of :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP1 :version_of :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :POP1 :version_of :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP1 :version_of :POP"},{"questionBody":"IsFormat_String_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Format_String_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Format_String_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Format_String_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :RTSP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RTSP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SSH"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :TFTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :TFTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :POP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Gopher_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gopher_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :NetBIOS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NetBIOS"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Finger_protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Finger_protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :HTTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :NAT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NAT"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :r_sync ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_sync"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Bit_Torrent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Bit_Torrent"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Telnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Telnet"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :STUN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :STUN"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Internet_Relay_Chat"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :SOAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SOAP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :BOOTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BOOTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :r_login ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :r_login"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Apple_Filing_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :RIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RIP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :FTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :FTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :DHCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DHCP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Gnutella ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Gnutella"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :NNTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :NNTP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :PPP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :Advance_Direct_Connect"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :DICT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DICT"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :DNS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :DNS"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :RDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RDP"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :BACnet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :BACnet"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :RADIUS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :RADIUS"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :HTTPS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :HTTPS"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication :uses :LDAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application :uses :LDAP"},{"questionBody":"IsFirewall :offers :System_Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :offers :System_Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Firewall :offers :System_Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :offers :System_Security"},{"questionBody":"IsFirewall :has :User_control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :User_control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :User_control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :User_control"},{"questionBody":"IsFirewall :has :Service_control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Service_control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Service_control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Service_control"},{"questionBody":"IsFirewall :has :Direction_control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Direction_control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Direction_control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Direction_control"},{"questionBody":"IsFirewall :has :Behaviour_control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Behaviour_control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Behaviour_control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Firewall :has :Behaviour_control"},{"questionBody":"IsSNMPv1 :version_of :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv1 :version_of :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNMPv1 :version_of :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv1 :version_of :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"IsCyber_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cyber_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cyber_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cyber_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsRC5 :approaches :Block_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RC5 :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RC5 :approaches :Block_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RC5 :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsSmurf_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Smurf_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Smurf_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Smurf_Attack :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsSDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet :uses CD ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses CD"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses CD"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses CD"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet :uses :Token_Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses :Token_Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses :Token_Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :uses :Token_Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet :is_a :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :is_a :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet :is_a :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :is_a :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet :invented_by :Xerox_PARC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :invented_by :Xerox_PARC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet :invented_by :Xerox_PARC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet :invented_by :Xerox_PARC"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_6 :version_of :Internet_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_6 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_6 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_6 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMetamorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Metamorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Metamorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Metamorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTC :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTC :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTC :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTC :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP2 :version_of :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP2 :version_of :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP2 :version_of :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP2 :version_of :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :access_to G ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :access_to G ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :uses IP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :uses IP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :uses IP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :uses IP"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :provides :VOIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :provides :VOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :provides :VOIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :provides :VOIP"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :service :eMail ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :service :eMail"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :service :eMail"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :service :eMail"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :access_to G ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :access_to G"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :called :ARPANET ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :called :ARPANET"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :called :ARPANET"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :called :ARPANET"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet :service :IPTV ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :service :IPTV"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet :service :IPTV"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet :service :IPTV"},{"questionBody":"IsVBR-RT :belongs_to :Type_2 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VBR-RT :belongs_to :Type_2"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VBR-RT :belongs_to :Type_2"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VBR-RT :belongs_to :Type_2"},{"questionBody":"IsTelnet :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Telnet :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Telnet :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Telnet :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMolniya :revolers_in :Molniya ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Molniya :revolers_in :Molniya"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Molniya :revolers_in :Molniya"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Molniya :revolers_in :Molniya"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-48 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-48 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-48 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-48 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsFTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsApple_Filing_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Apple_Filing_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Apple_Filing_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Apple_Filing_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsVRP :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VRP :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VRP :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VRP :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsVRP :invented_by :Huawei ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VRP :invented_by :Huawei"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VRP :invented_by :Huawei"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VRP :invented_by :Huawei"},{"questionBody":"IsStar_Mesh :extension_of :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsStar_Mesh :extension_of :Mesh ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Mesh"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Mesh"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Star_Mesh :extension_of :Mesh"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :Skype_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :Skype_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :Skype_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :Skype_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :H.323 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :H.323"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :H.323"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :H.323"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :RTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :RTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :RTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :RTP"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :utilize :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :utilize :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :utilize :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :utilize :Internet"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :MGCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :MGCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :MGCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :MGCP"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :IAX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :IAX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :IAX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :IAX"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :SIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SIP"},{"questionBody":"IsVOIP :uses :SDP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SDP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SDP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VOIP :uses :SDP"},{"questionBody":"IsStatistical_Anomaly_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Statistical_Anomaly_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Statistical_Anomaly_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Statistical_Anomaly_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsRADIUS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RADIUS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RADIUS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RADIUS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsArbitrated_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Arbitrated_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Arbitrated_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Arbitrated_DS :kind_of :Digital_Signature"},{"questionBody":"IsRadiating :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radiating :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Radiating :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radiating :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsBACnet :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsBACnet :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BACnet :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsGopher_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gopher_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Gopher_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gopher_Protocol :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMesh :made_of :Partially_Connected ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Partially_Connected"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Partially_Connected"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Partially_Connected"},{"questionBody":"IsMesh :made_of :Fully_Connected ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Fully_Connected"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Fully_Connected"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mesh :made_of :Fully_Connected"},{"questionBody":"IsScreened_Host_Firewall :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Host_Firewall :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Screened_Host_Firewall :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Host_Firewall :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsAudit_Record :include :Native ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Native"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Native"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Native"},{"questionBody":"IsAudit_Record :include :Detection_Specific ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Detection_Specific"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Detection_Specific"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :include :Detection_Specific"},{"questionBody":"IsAudit_Record :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Audit_Record :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsPM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :PM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork :functions :Logical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Logical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork :functions :Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Routing"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork :functions :Forwarding ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :functions :Forwarding"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"IsBing :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bing :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bing :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bing :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsCircuit_Mode :types_of :Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Mode :types_of :Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Circuit_Mode :types_of :Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Mode :types_of :Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsSSH.2 :version_of :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSH.2 :version_of :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SSH.2 :version_of :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSH.2 :version_of :SSH"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTN :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTN :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTN :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTN :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsHTTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :HTTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsHTTP :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTP :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :HTTP :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTP :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :transmits :Datagrams ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :transmits :Datagrams"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :transmits :Datagrams"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :transmits :Datagrams"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :functions :Service_Point_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Service_Point_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Service_Point_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Service_Point_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :functions :Segmentation_and_Reassembly ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Segmentation_and_Reassembly"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Segmentation_and_Reassembly"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Segmentation_and_Reassembly"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport :functions :Connection_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Connection_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Connection_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport :functions :Connection_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsBastion_Host :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bastion_Host :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bastion_Host :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bastion_Host :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsSQL_Injection :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SQL_Injection :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SQL_Injection :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SQL_Injection :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsCISCO_IOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsCISCO_IOS :invented_by :Cisco_Inc. ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :invented_by :Cisco_Inc."},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :invented_by :Cisco_Inc."}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CISCO_IOS :invented_by :Cisco_Inc."},{"questionBody":"IsAccess_Switch :kind_of :Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :kind_of :Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Access_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsSFTP :kind_of :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SFTP :kind_of :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SFTP :kind_of :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SFTP :kind_of :SSH"},{"questionBody":"IsRadio_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Radio_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"},{"questionBody":"IsPort_Scanner :kind_of :Passive_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Port_Scanner :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Port_Scanner :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Port_Scanner :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsTwinaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twinaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Twinaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twinaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_2012 :version_of :Windows_Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2012 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_2012 :version_of :Windows_Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2012 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTH :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTH :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTH :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTH :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Relay_Chat :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Relay_Chat :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Relay_Chat :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Relay_Chat :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsX.25 :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :X.25 :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :X.25 :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :X.25 :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"IsDistributed_Star :types_of :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_Star :types_of :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distributed_Star :types_of :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_Star :types_of :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsMisuse_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Misuse_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Misuse_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Misuse_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsJitter :utilize :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Jitter :utilize :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Jitter :utilize :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Jitter :utilize :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsGoogle :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Google :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Google :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Google :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsUnidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Unidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"questionBody":"Isr_sync :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :r_sync :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :r_sync :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :r_sync :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsEthernet_Hub :kind_of :Hub ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :kind_of :Hub"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Ethernet_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"questionBody":"IsReplay :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Replay :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Replay :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Replay :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsRG6 :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RG6 :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RG6 :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RG6 :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsCat3 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat3 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cat3 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat3 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"questionBody":"IsFHSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FHSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FHSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FHSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"questionBody":"IsFHSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FHSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FHSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FHSS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol :transmits :Packet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :transmits :Packet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :transmits :Packet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :transmits :Packet"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol :offers :Connectionless_Service ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :offers :Connectionless_Service"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :offers :Connectionless_Service"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :offers :Connectionless_Service"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol :is_a :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :is_a :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :is_a :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol :is_a :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Intranet_VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Intranet_VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Intranet_VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Intranet_VPN"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :offers :System_Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :offers :System_Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :offers :System_Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :offers :System_Security"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :need :Tunnelling ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :need :Tunnelling"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :need :Tunnelling"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :need :Tunnelling"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize TLS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize TLS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize TLS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize TLS"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :MPPE ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :MPPE"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :MPPE"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :MPPE"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPP"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSTP"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :IPSec ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :IPSec"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :IPSec"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :IPSec"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :PPTP"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :L2TP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :L2TP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :L2TP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :L2TP"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Extranet_VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Extranet_VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Extranet_VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Extranet_VPN"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :SSH"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :utilize :DTLS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :DTLS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :DTLS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :utilize :DTLS"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Remote_access_VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Remote_access_VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Remote_access_VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Private_Network :classify_as :Remote_access_VPN"},{"questionBody":"IsTriaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Triaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Triaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Triaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsTransmission_Control_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :uses :Internet_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsTransmission_Control_Protocol :offers :Connection_Oriented_Service ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :offers :Connection_Oriented_Service"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :offers :Connection_Oriented_Service"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transmission_Control_Protocol :offers :Connection_Oriented_Service"},{"questionBody":"IsLatency :utilize :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Latency :utilize :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Latency :utilize :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Latency :utilize :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsNNTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NNTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :NNTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NNTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMozilla_Firefox :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mozilla_Firefox :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Mozilla_Firefox :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Mozilla_Firefox :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsElliptical :revolers_in :Elliptical ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Elliptical :revolers_in :Elliptical"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Elliptical :revolers_in :Elliptical"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Elliptical :revolers_in :Elliptical"},{"questionBody":null,"questionType":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null,"bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":null},{"questionBody":"IsCircuit_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Circuit_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Circuit_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsBuffer_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Buffer_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Buffer_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Buffer_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsSC-FDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SC-FDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SC-FDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SC-FDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsGoogle_Chrome :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Google_Chrome :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Google_Chrome :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Google_Chrome :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsFM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"Is_a_OFDM_Waveform :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_a_OFDM_Waveform :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_a_OFDM_Waveform :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_a_OFDM_Waveform :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsModification_of_Message :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modification_of_Message :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Modification_of_Message :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modification_of_Message :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-768 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-768 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-768 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-768 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsIntrusion_Detection_System :offers :System_Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :offers :System_Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :offers :System_Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :offers :System_Security"},{"questionBody":"IsIntrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Target_Based_IDS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Target_Based_IDS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Target_Based_IDS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Target_Based_IDS"},{"questionBody":"IsIntrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Network_Based_IDS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Network_Based_IDS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Network_Based_IDS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Network_Based_IDS"},{"questionBody":"IsIntrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Host_Based_IDS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Host_Based_IDS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Host_Based_IDS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Host_Based_IDS"},{"questionBody":"IsIntrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Application_Based_IDS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Application_Based_IDS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Application_Based_IDS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Intrusion_Detection_System :classify_as :Application_Based_IDS"},{"questionBody":"IsShared_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shared_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Shared_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shared_Fiber :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsSNMPv3 :version_of :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv3 :version_of :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNMPv3 :version_of :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv3 :version_of :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"Is :approaches :Stream_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsScreened_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Screened_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsParasitic_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Parasitic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Parasitic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Parasitic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsLocal_Area_Network :classify_as :Storage_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Storage_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Storage_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Storage_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsLocal_Area_Network :classify_as :Home_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Home_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Home_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Local_Area_Network :classify_as :Home_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsBidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bidirectional_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"questionBody":"IsBiaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Biaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Biaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Biaxial :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsVG-Any_LAN :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VG-Any_LAN :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :VG-Any_LAN :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :VG-Any_LAN :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsPeer_to_Peer :types_of :Network_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Peer_to_Peer :types_of :Network_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Peer_to_Peer :types_of :Network_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Peer_to_Peer :types_of :Network_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"Is_b :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_b :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_b :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_b :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsHotmail :provides :eMail ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hotmail :provides :eMail"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hotmail :provides :eMail"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hotmail :provides :eMail"},{"questionBody":"IsModification :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modification :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Modification :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modification :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsJUNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JUNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :JUNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JUNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsJUNOS :invented_by :Jupiter_Networks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JUNOS :invented_by :Jupiter_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :JUNOS :invented_by :Jupiter_Networks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JUNOS :invented_by :Jupiter_Networks"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :uses P ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses P"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :uses P"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses P"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :uses :SOCKS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SOCKS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SOCKS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SOCKS"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :uses :SMB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SMB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SMB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :SMB"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :uses :NFS ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NFS"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NFS"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NFS"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :uses :NCP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NCP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NCP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :uses :NCP"},{"questionBody":"IsSession :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Session :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Session :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsBASET4 :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET4 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASET4 :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET4 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsSNTP :version_of :NTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNTP :version_of :NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNTP :version_of :NTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNTP :version_of :NTP"},{"questionBody":"IsArchived_Gateway :types_of :Gateway ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Archived_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"questionBody":"IsSpoofing :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Spoofing :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Spoofing :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Spoofing :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsDOS :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DOS :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DOS :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DOS :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsAES :approaches :Block_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AES :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AES :approaches :Block_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AES :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsEdge_Router :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsLow_Earth_Orbit :revolers_in :Low_Earth_Orbit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Low_Earth_Orbit :revolers_in :Low_Earth_Orbit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Low_Earth_Orbit :revolers_in :Low_Earth_Orbit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Low_Earth_Orbit :revolers_in :Low_Earth_Orbit"},{"questionBody":"IsSMTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SMTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SMTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SMTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsOrginal_IMAP :version_of :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Orginal_IMAP :version_of :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Orginal_IMAP :version_of :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Orginal_IMAP :version_of :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsBlock_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Block_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Block_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Block_Cipher :kind_of :Symmetrie_Encryption"},{"questionBody":"IsGigabit_Ethernet :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gigabit_Ethernet :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Gigabit_Ethernet :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gigabit_Ethernet :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-24 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-24 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-24 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-24 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"Is_n :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_n :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_n :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_n :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsPolymorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Polymorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Polymorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Polymorphic_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Zero_Day_Exploit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Zero_Day_Exploit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Zero_Day_Exploit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Zero_Day_Exploit"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Ultrafast_Spreading ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Ultrafast_Spreading"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Ultrafast_Spreading"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Ultrafast_Spreading"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Transport_Vehicles ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Transport_Vehicles"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Transport_Vehicles"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Transport_Vehicles"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Polymorphic ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Polymorphic"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Polymorphic"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Polymorphic"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Multiplatform ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multiplatform"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multiplatform"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multiplatform"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Multi_Exploit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multi_Exploit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multi_Exploit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Multi_Exploit"},{"questionBody":"IsWorm :include :Metamorphic ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Metamorphic"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Metamorphic"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Worm :include :Metamorphic"},{"questionBody":"IsDNS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DNS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DNS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DNS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_Server :kind_of Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_Server :kind_of Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_Server :kind_of Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_Server :kind_of Server"},{"questionBody":"IsShielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"Is :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsAnomaly_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Anomaly_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Anomaly_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Anomaly_Detection :functions :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsIETF :improve :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IETF :improve :Internet"},{"questionBody":"IsMemory_Resident_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Memory_Resident_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Memory_Resident_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Memory_Resident_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsPacket_Fittering_Routers :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsPacket_Fittering_Routers :has :Positive_Filter ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Positive_Filter"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Positive_Filter"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Positive_Filter"},{"questionBody":"IsPacket_Fittering_Routers :has :Negative_Filter ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Negative_Filter"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Negative_Filter"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Fittering_Routers :has :Negative_Filter"},{"questionBody":"IsPublic_Key_Encryption :offers :Public_Key_Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :offers :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :offers :Public_Key_Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :offers :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsPublic_Key_Encryption :classify_as :RSA ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :RSA"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :RSA"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :RSA"},{"questionBody":"IsPublic_Key_Encryption :classify_as :IES ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :IES"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :IES"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :IES"},{"questionBody":"IsPublic_Key_Encryption :classify_as :Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Encryption :classify_as :Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsAAL :layer_of :ATM ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :layer_of :ATM"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AAL :layer_of :ATM"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :layer_of :ATM"},{"questionBody":"IsAAL :classify_as  ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as "},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as "}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as "},{"questionBody":"IsAAL :classify_as :Type_5 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_5"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_5"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_5"},{"questionBody":"IsAAL :classify_as :Type_2 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_2"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_2"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_2"},{"questionBody":"IsAAL :classify_as :Type_1 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_1"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_1"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AAL :classify_as :Type_1"},{"questionBody":"IsTwisted_Ribbon_Cable :kind_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Ribbon_Cable :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Twisted_Ribbon_Cable :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Ribbon_Cable :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsBlowfish :approaches :Block_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Blowfish :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Blowfish :approaches :Block_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Blowfish :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsRepeater_Hub :kind_of :Hub ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :kind_of :Hub"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"questionBody":"IsSDH :provides :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :provides :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SDH :provides :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :provides :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsSDH :classify_as :Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Unidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsSDH :classify_as :Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Linear_Automatic_Protection_Switching"},{"questionBody":"IsSDH :classify_as :Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SDH :classify_as :Bidirectional_Path_Switching_Ring"},{"questionBody":"IsClass_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_Fa :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsLDAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :LDAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :LDAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :LDAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsInterplay_Factors :utilize :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interplay_Factors :utilize :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Interplay_Factors :utilize :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interplay_Factors :utilize :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsStateful_Inspection_Forward :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stateful_Inspection_Forward :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Stateful_Inspection_Forward :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stateful_Inspection_Forward :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsIANA :allocate :Internet_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IANA :allocate :Internet_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IANA :allocate :Internet_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IANA :allocate :Internet_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsCat5 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat5 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cat5 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat5 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"questionBody":"IsDialog_Control :functions :Session ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Dialog_Control :functions :Session"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dialog_Control :functions :Session"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Dialog_Control :functions :Session"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :made_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :contains :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :classify_as :Scope ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scope"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scope"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :made_of IP_Suite ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of IP_Suite"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of IP_Suite"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :made_of IP_Suite"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :classify_as :Scale ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scale"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scale"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Scale"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :utilize :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :utilize :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :utilize :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :utilize :Communication_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :need :Network_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Network_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Network_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Network_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :has :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :has :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :has :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :has :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :contains :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :contains :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :need :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :need :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsComputer_Networks :classify_as :Topology ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Topology"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Topology"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Computer_Networks :classify_as :Topology"},{"questionBody":"IsSymmetrie_Encryption :kind_of :Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Symmetrie_Encryption :kind_of :Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Symmetrie_Encryption :kind_of :Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Symmetrie_Encryption :kind_of :Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTB :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTB :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTB :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTB :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsRelease_of_Message_Content :include :Passive_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Release_of_Message_Content :include :Passive_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Release_of_Message_Content :include :Passive_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Release_of_Message_Content :include :Passive_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsSatellites :uses :Wireless ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :uses :Wireless"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Satellites :uses :Wireless"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :uses :Wireless"},{"questionBody":"IsSatellites :located :Molniya ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Molniya"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Molniya"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Molniya"},{"questionBody":"IsSatellites :located :Low_Earth_Orbit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Low_Earth_Orbit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Low_Earth_Orbit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Low_Earth_Orbit"},{"questionBody":"IsSatellites :located :Geostationary ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Geostationary"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Geostationary"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Geostationary"},{"questionBody":"IsSatellites :located :Elliptical ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Elliptical"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Elliptical"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Satellites :located :Elliptical"},{"questionBody":"Is_g :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_g :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_g :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_g :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsRC4 :approaches :Stream_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RC4 :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RC4 :approaches :Stream_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RC4 :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Wide_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Wide_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Wide_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Wide_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Personal_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Personal_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Personal_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Personal_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Metropolitan_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Metropolitan_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Metropolitan_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Metropolitan_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Local_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Local_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Local_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Local_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Campus_Area_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Campus_Area_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Campus_Area_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Campus_Area_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsScale :classify_as :Backbone_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Backbone_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Backbone_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scale :classify_as :Backbone_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_2008 :version_of :Windows_Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2008 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_2008 :version_of :Windows_Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2008 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"questionBody":"IsEncryption :functions :Presentation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Encryption :functions :Presentation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Encryption :functions :Presentation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Encryption :functions :Presentation"},{"questionBody":"IsResearch_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Research_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Research_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Research_Honeypots :kind_of :Honeypots"},{"questionBody":"IsPPP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PPP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :PPP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :PPP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsCoaxial_Cable :types_of Guided_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :types_of Guided_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :types_of Guided_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :types_of Guided_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsCoaxial_Cable :transmits :Radio_Frequency_Signals ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :transmits :Radio_Frequency_Signals"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :transmits :Radio_Frequency_Signals"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :transmits :Radio_Frequency_Signals"},{"questionBody":"IsCoaxial_Cable :invented_by :Oliver_Heaviside ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :invented_by :Oliver_Heaviside"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :invented_by :Oliver_Heaviside"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Coaxial_Cable :invented_by :Oliver_Heaviside"},{"questionBody":"IsBASEX :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEX :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASEX :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEX :kind_of :Gigabit_Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTP :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTP :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTP :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTP :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_2000 :version_of :Windows_Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2000 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_2000 :version_of :Windows_Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_2000 :version_of :Windows_Server"},{"questionBody":"IsDistributed_IDS :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_IDS :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distributed_IDS :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_IDS :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Networking :include :Distribution_Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Networking :include :Distribution_Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Networking :include :Distribution_Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Networking :include :Distribution_Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsSSH :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSH :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SSH :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSH :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsGeostationary :revolers_in :Geostationary ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Geostationary :revolers_in :Geostationary"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Geostationary :revolers_in :Geostationary"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Geostationary :revolers_in :Geostationary"},{"questionBody":"IsZyNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsZyNOS :invented_by :Zyxel ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :invented_by :Zyxel"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :invented_by :Zyxel"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ZyNOS :invented_by :Zyxel"},{"questionBody":"IsPOP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :POP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsRule_Based_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Rule_Based_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Rule_Based_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Rule_Based_Detection :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsDHCP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsDHCP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DHCP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsCore_Switch :kind_of :Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :kind_of :Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Switch :kind_of :Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsWDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :WDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :WDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :WDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"questionBody":"IsMultiport_Hub :kind_of :Hub ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :kind_of :Hub"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Multiport_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"questionBody":"IsIAB :manage :IRTF ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IRTF"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IRTF"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IRTF"},{"questionBody":"IsIAB :manage :IETF ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IETF"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IETF"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IAB :manage :IETF"},{"questionBody":"IsIDEA :approaches :Block_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IDEA :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IDEA :approaches :Block_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IDEA :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-12 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-12 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-12 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-12 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-1 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-1 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-1 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-1 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsServer :types_of :Network_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Server :types_of :Network_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Server :types_of :Network_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Server :types_of :Network_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsCompression :functions :Presentation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Compression :functions :Presentation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Compression :functions :Presentation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Compression :functions :Presentation"},{"questionBody":"IsCSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :CSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"questionBody":"IsPacket_Mode :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Mode :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Packet_Mode :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Packet_Mode :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Hub :kind_of :Hub ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :kind_of :Hub"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Hub :kind_of :Hub"},{"questionBody":"IsIPTV :offers :Video_on_Demand ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Video_on_Demand"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Video_on_Demand"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Video_on_Demand"},{"questionBody":"IsIPTV :offers :Time_Shifted_TV ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Time_Shifted_TV"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Time_Shifted_TV"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Time_Shifted_TV"},{"questionBody":"IsIPTV :offers :Live_TV ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Live_TV"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Live_TV"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IPTV :offers :Live_TV"},{"questionBody":"IsExtremeXOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsExtremeXOS :invented_by :Extreme_Network ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :invented_by :Extreme_Network"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :invented_by :Extreme_Network"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ExtremeXOS :invented_by :Extreme_Network"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Explorer :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Explorer :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Explorer :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Explorer :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsHTML :offers :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTML :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :HTML :offers :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTML :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsLinear_Bus :kind_of :Bus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Linear_Bus :kind_of :Bus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Linear_Bus :kind_of :Bus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Linear_Bus :kind_of :Bus"},{"questionBody":"IsSwitch :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Switch :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsSwitch :functions :Store_and_Forward ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Store_and_Forward"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Store_and_Forward"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Store_and_Forward"},{"questionBody":"IsSwitch :functions :Fragment_Free ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Fragment_Free"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Fragment_Free"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Fragment_Free"},{"questionBody":"IsSwitch :functions :Cut_Through ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Cut_Through"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Cut_Through"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Cut_Through"},{"questionBody":"IsSwitch :functions :Adaptive_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Adaptive_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Adaptive_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Switch :functions :Adaptive_Switching"},{"questionBody":"IsLoaded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Loaded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Loaded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Loaded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsRadio_and_Spread_Spectrum :uses :Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :uses :Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :uses :Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :uses :Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsRadio_and_Spread_Spectrum :kind_of :Wireless ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :kind_of :Wireless"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :kind_of :Wireless"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum :kind_of :Wireless"},{"questionBody":"IsNetBIOS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsNetBIOS :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NetBIOS :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsHash_and_Mac_Algebra :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsBandwidth :improve :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bandwidth :improve :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bandwidth :improve :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bandwidth :improve :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsTDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :TDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :TDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :TDM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"questionBody":"IsPublic_Key_Cryptography :kind_of :Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Cryptography :kind_of :Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Cryptography :kind_of :Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Public_Key_Cryptography :kind_of :Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsModem :need :ISP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modem :need :ISP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Modem :need :ISP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modem :need :ISP"},{"questionBody":"IsModem :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modem :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Modem :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Modem :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsPhysical_Layer :layer_of :ATM ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Layer :layer_of :ATM"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Physical_Layer :layer_of :ATM"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Physical_Layer :layer_of :ATM"},{"questionBody":"IsOpera :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Opera :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Opera :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Opera :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsDICT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DICT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DICT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DICT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsGuided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Guided_Media :part_of :Communication_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsQAM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :QAM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :QAM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :QAM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"IsPassive_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Passive_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Passive_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Passive_Optical_Network :distribution :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-192 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-192 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-192 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-192 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsCMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :CMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"},{"questionBody":"IsTwisted_Pair :types_of Guided_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :types_of Guided_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :types_of Guided_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twisted_Pair :types_of Guided_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsBASEFX :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEFX :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASEFX :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEFX :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsSpatial_OAM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Spatial_OAM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Spatial_OAM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Spatial_OAM :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"questionBody":"IsBrouter :made_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsBrouter :made_of :Bridge ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Bridge"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :made_of :Bridge"},{"questionBody":"IsBrouter :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Brouter :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Brouter :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsGmail :provides :eMail ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gmail :provides :eMail"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Gmail :provides :eMail"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gmail :provides :eMail"},{"questionBody":"IsMasquerade :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Masquerade :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Masquerade :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Masquerade :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsHTTPS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTPS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :HTTPS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HTTPS :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsRepeater :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsRepeater :classify_as :Wifi_Repeater ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :Wifi_Repeater"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :Wifi_Repeater"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :Wifi_Repeater"},{"questionBody":"IsRepeater :classify_as :LAN_Repeater ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :LAN_Repeater"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :LAN_Repeater"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Repeater :classify_as :LAN_Repeater"},{"questionBody":"IsBASE2 :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASE2 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASE2 :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASE2 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Physical_Addressing"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Flow_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Flow_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Media_Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Logical_Link_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :has :Media_Access_Control_Sublayer"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Access_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Access_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Framing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Framing"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Error_Control ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Error_Control"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :functions :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :functions :Frames"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Link :transmits :Frames ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Link :transmits :Frames"},{"questionBody":"IsAM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :AM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :AM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"IsRIP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RIP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :RIP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :RIP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Is_ad :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_ad :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :_ad :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :_ad :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsCBR :belongs_to :Type_1 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CBR :belongs_to :Type_1"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :CBR :belongs_to :Type_1"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :CBR :belongs_to :Type_1"},{"questionBody":"IsClass_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Class_F :types_of :Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"Isr_login :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :r_login :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :r_login :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :r_login :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsStatistical_Multiplexing :types_of :Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Statistical_Multiplexing :types_of :Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Statistical_Multiplexing :types_of :Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Statistical_Multiplexing :types_of :Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsScreened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Screened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Screened_Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsPOP3 :version_of :POP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP3 :version_of :POP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :POP3 :version_of :POP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :POP3 :version_of :POP"},{"questionBody":"IsPresentation :layer_of :OSI_Model ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Presentation :layer_of :OSI_Model"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Society :publish :RFC ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :publish :RFC"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Society :committee :IAB ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Society :committee :IAB"},{"questionBody":"IsDigital_Signature :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Digital_Signature :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Digital_Signature :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Digital_Signature :improve :Public_Key_Cryptography"},{"questionBody":"IsOptical_Fibre :types_of Guided_Media ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :types_of Guided_Media"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :types_of Guided_Media"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :types_of Guided_Media"},{"questionBody":"IsOptical_Fibre :made_of Plastics ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :made_of Plastics"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :made_of Plastics"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Fibre :made_of Plastics"},{"questionBody":"IsUnshielded_Twisted_Pain :types_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain :types_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsSTS-3 :version_of SDH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-3 :version_of SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STS-3 :version_of SDH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STS-3 :version_of SDH"},{"questionBody":"IsSIP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsSIP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SIP :uses :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMIME :extension_of :SMTP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MIME :extension_of :SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :MIME :extension_of :SMTP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MIME :extension_of :SMTP"},{"questionBody":"IsExtended_Star :types_of :Star ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extended_Star :types_of :Star"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extended_Star :types_of :Star"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extended_Star :types_of :Star"},{"questionBody":"IsFabrication :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Fabrication :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Fabrication :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Fabrication :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsTwitter :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twitter :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Twitter :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Twitter :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsGateway :access_to :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gateway :access_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Gateway :access_to :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gateway :access_to :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP4 :version_of :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP4 :version_of :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP4 :version_of :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP4 :version_of :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsIdle_Scan :kind_of :Passive_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Idle_Scan :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Idle_Scan :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Idle_Scan :kind_of :Passive_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsSemirigid :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Semirigid :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Semirigid :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Semirigid :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsIP_Suite :made_of :Transport_Layer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Transport_Layer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Transport_Layer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Transport_Layer"},{"questionBody":"IsIP_Suite :made_of :Network_Interface ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Network_Interface"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Network_Interface"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Network_Interface"},{"questionBody":"IsIP_Suite :made_of :Internet_Layer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Internet_Layer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Internet_Layer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Internet_Layer"},{"questionBody":"IsIP_Suite :made_of :Application_Layer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Application_Layer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Application_Layer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :made_of :Application_Layer"},{"questionBody":"IsIP_Suite :deployed_in :Computer_Networks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IP_Suite :deployed_in :Computer_Networks"},{"questionBody":"IsStealth_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stealth_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Stealth_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Stealth_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsWindows_for_Workgroup :approaches :Peer_to_Peer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_for_Workgroup :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Windows_for_Workgroup :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Windows_for_Workgroup :approaches :Peer_to_Peer"},{"questionBody":"IsTHSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :THSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :THSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :THSS :types_of :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"questionBody":"IsBASET2 :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET2 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASET2 :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASET2 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Level_Gateway :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsIEEE_802.11 :service :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :service :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :service :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :service :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsIEEE_802.11 :provides :Wireless ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :provides :Wireless"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :provides :Wireless"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IEEE_802.11 :provides :Wireless"},{"questionBody":"Is :approaches :Stream_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :approaches :Stream_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsSNMPv2 :version_of :SNMP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv2 :version_of :SNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SNMPv2 :version_of :SNMP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SNMPv2 :version_of :SNMP"},{"questionBody":"IsSynchronazation_Gateway :types_of :Gateway ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronazation_Gateway :types_of :Gateway"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTX :types_of :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTX :types_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTX :types_of :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTX :types_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsYahoo_Mail :provides :eMail ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Yahoo_Mail :provides :eMail"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Yahoo_Mail :provides :eMail"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Yahoo_Mail :provides :eMail"},{"questionBody":"IsWorld_Wide_Web :offers :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :offers :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsWorld_Wide_Web :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsWorld_Wide_Web :contains :URL ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URL"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URL"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URL"},{"questionBody":"IsWorld_Wide_Web :contains :URI ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URI"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URI"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :contains :URI"},{"questionBody":"IsWorld_Wide_Web :access_to :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :access_to :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :access_to :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :World_Wide_Web :access_to :Internet"},{"questionBody":"IsTFTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :TFTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :TFTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :TFTP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsHoneypots :types_of :Honeypots ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Honeypots :types_of :Honeypots"},{"questionBody":"IsHoneypots :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Honeypots :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Honeypots :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Honeypots :approaches :Intrusion_Detection_System"},{"questionBody":"IsFTTD :types_of :FTTX ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTD :types_of :FTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :FTTD :types_of :FTTX"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :FTTD :types_of :FTTX"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP3 :version_of :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP3 :version_of :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP3 :version_of :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP3 :version_of :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsBASE5 :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASE5 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASE5 :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASE5 :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsMultimode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Multimode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Multimode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Multimode_Fiber :part_of :Optical_Fibre"},{"questionBody":"IsTraffic_Analysis :perfoms :Passive_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Traffic_Analysis :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Traffic_Analysis :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Traffic_Analysis :perfoms :Passive_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsHigher_Layer_Protocols :layer_of :ATM ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Higher_Layer_Protocols :layer_of :ATM"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Higher_Layer_Protocols :layer_of :ATM"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Higher_Layer_Protocols :layer_of :ATM"},{"questionBody":"IsBonded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bonded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bonded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bonded_TP :kind_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :classify_as :Orginal_IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :Orginal_IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :Orginal_IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :Orginal_IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :classify_as :IMAP4 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP4"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP4"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP4"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :classify_as :IMAP3 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP3"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP3"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP3"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :classify_as :IMAP2bis ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2bis"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2bis"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2bis"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP :classify_as :IMAP2 ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP :classify_as :IMAP2"},{"questionBody":"IsSTUN :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STUN :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :STUN :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :STUN :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :version_of :Internet_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :version_of :Internet_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_E ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_E"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_E"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_E"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_D ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_D"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_D"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_D"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_C ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_C"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_C"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_C"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_B ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_B"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_B"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_B"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_A ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_A"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_A"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Protocol_Version_4 :classify_as :Class_A"},{"questionBody":"IsBoot_Sector_Virus :kind_of :Virus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Boot_Sector_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Boot_Sector_Virus :kind_of :Virus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Boot_Sector_Virus :kind_of :Virus"},{"questionBody":"IsData_Center_Switches :is_a :Core_Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Center_Switches :is_a :Core_Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Data_Center_Switches :is_a :Core_Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Data_Center_Switches :is_a :Core_Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsMC-SS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MC-SS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :MC-SS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MC-SS :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsOptical_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Optical_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Optical_Repeaters :types_of :LAN_Repeater"},{"questionBody":"IsDES :approaches :Block_Cipher ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DES :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :DES :approaches :Block_Cipher"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :DES :approaches :Block_Cipher"},{"questionBody":"IsWireless_Router :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Wireless_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsSSB :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSB :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SSB :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SSB :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"IsAvailablity :include :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Availablity :include :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Availablity :include :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Availablity :include :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsWLAN :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :WLAN :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :WLAN :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :WLAN :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsCore_Router :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Core_Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Core_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication_Layer :uses :Port_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :uses :Port_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :uses :Port_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :uses :Port_Address"},{"questionBody":"IsApplication_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Application_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"questionBody":"IsSynchronization :functions :Session ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronization :functions :Session"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Synchronization :functions :Session"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Synchronization :functions :Session"},{"questionBody":"IsSafari :access_to :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Safari :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Safari :access_to :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Safari :access_to :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Interface :uses :MAC_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :uses :MAC_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :uses :MAC_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :uses :MAC_Address"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Interface :layer_of IP_Suite ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :layer_of IP_Suite"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Interface :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"questionBody":"IsSingle_Homed_Bastion :secure :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Single_Homed_Bastion :secure :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Single_Homed_Bastion :secure :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Single_Homed_Bastion :secure :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsInterruption :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interruption :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Interruption :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Interruption :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsHMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :HMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :HMAC :perfoms :Hash_and_Mac_Algebra"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Layer :uses :IP_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :uses :IP_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :uses :IP_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :uses :IP_Address"},{"questionBody":"IsInternet_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Internet_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"questionBody":"IsSubscriber_Edge_Router :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Subscriber_Edge_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsMOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :MOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MOS :types_of :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsMOS :invented_by :Alcatel-Lucent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MOS :invented_by :Alcatel-Lucent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :MOS :invented_by :Alcatel-Lucent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :MOS :invented_by :Alcatel-Lucent"},{"questionBody":"IsCloud_Managed_Access_Switch :is_a :Access_Switch ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cloud_Managed_Access_Switch :is_a :Access_Switch"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cloud_Managed_Access_Switch :is_a :Access_Switch"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cloud_Managed_Access_Switch :is_a :Access_Switch"},{"questionBody":"IsHub :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hub :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hub :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hub :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport_Layer :uses :Socket_Address ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :uses :Socket_Address"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :uses :Socket_Address"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :uses :Socket_Address"},{"questionBody":"IsTransport_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Transport_Layer :layer_of IP_Suite"},{"questionBody":"IsInfrared :offers :Wireless ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Infrared :offers :Wireless"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Infrared :offers :Wireless"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Infrared :offers :Wireless"},{"questionBody":"IsNAT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NAT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :NAT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NAT :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsCongession :utilize :Performance ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Congession :utilize :Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Congession :utilize :Performance"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Congession :utilize :Performance"},{"questionBody":"IsExtranet :has :VPN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :VPN"},{"questionBody":"IsExtranet :has :Firewall ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Extranet :has :Firewall"},{"questionBody":"IsJSP :offers :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JSP :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :JSP :offers :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :JSP :offers :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsRigid_Line :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Rigid_Line :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Rigid_Line :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Rigid_Line :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsDistributed_Bus :kind_of :Bus ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_Bus :kind_of :Bus"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Distributed_Bus :kind_of :Bus"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Distributed_Bus :kind_of :Bus"},{"questionBody":"IsCat4 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat4 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cat4 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cat4 :kind_of :Unshielded_Twisted_Pain"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Operating_System :service :Computer_Networks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :service :Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :service :Computer_Networks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :service :Computer_Networks"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Operating_System :classify_as Server ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as Server"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as Server"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as Server"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Operating_System :classify_as :Router_Operating_System ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Router_Operating_System"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Router_Operating_System"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Router_Operating_System"},{"questionBody":"IsNetwork_Operating_System :classify_as :Peer_to_Peer ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Peer_to_Peer"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Peer_to_Peer"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Network_Operating_System :classify_as :Peer_to_Peer"},{"questionBody":"IsVariable_Bit_Rate :belongs_to  ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Variable_Bit_Rate :belongs_to "},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Variable_Bit_Rate :belongs_to "}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Variable_Bit_Rate :belongs_to "},{"questionBody":"IsPolarization_Multiplexing :kind_of :Circuit_Mode ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Polarization_Multiplexing :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Polarization_Multiplexing :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Polarization_Multiplexing :kind_of :Circuit_Mode"},{"questionBody":"IsConfidentiality :include :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Confidentiality :include :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Confidentiality :include :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Confidentiality :include :Security"},{"questionBody":"Is :belongs_to :WLAN ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following : :belongs_to :WLAN"},{"questionBody":"IsScope :classify_as :Intranet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Intranet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Intranet"},{"questionBody":"IsScope :classify_as :Internet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Internet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Internet"},{"questionBody":"IsScope :classify_as :Extranet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Extranet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Extranet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Scope :classify_as :Extranet"},{"questionBody":"IsIntegrity :include :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Integrity :include :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Integrity :include :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Integrity :include :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsHeap_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Heap_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Heap_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Heap_Overflow :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsInter_Provider_Border_Router :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Inter_Provider_Border_Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsIMAP2bis :version_of :IMAP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP2bis :version_of :IMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :IMAP2bis :version_of :IMAP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :IMAP2bis :version_of :IMAP"},{"questionBody":"IsFacebook :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Facebook :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Facebook :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Facebook :deployed_in :World_Wide_Web"},{"questionBody":"IsGnutella :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gnutella :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Gnutella :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Gnutella :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :perfoms :Static_Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Static_Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Static_Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Static_Routing"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :perfoms :Link_State_Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Link_State_Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Link_State_Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Link_State_Routing"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :perfoms :Dynamic_Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Dynamic_Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Dynamic_Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Dynamic_Routing"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :perfoms :Distance_Vector_Routing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Distance_Vector_Routing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Distance_Vector_Routing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :perfoms :Distance_Vector_Routing"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :manage :Routing_table ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :manage :Routing_table"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :manage :Routing_table"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :manage :Routing_table"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :kind_of :Router ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Router"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Router"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Router"},{"questionBody":"IsRouter :kind_of :Networking_Hardware ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Router :kind_of :Networking_Hardware"},{"questionBody":"IsDynamic_TDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_TDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Dynamic_TDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Dynamic_TDM :kind_of :Statistical_Multiplexing"},{"questionBody":"IsNTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :NTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :NTP :uses :User_Datagram_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsVirtual_Path :uses :Virtual_Circuit ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Path :uses :Virtual_Circuit"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Virtual_Path :uses :Virtual_Circuit"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Virtual_Path :uses :Virtual_Circuit"},{"questionBody":"IsPoint_to_Point :classify_as :Switched ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Switched"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Switched"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Switched"},{"questionBody":"IsPoint_to_Point :classify_as :Permanent ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Permanent"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Permanent"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Point_to_Point :classify_as :Permanent"},{"questionBody":"IsBASEF :version_of :Ethernet ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEF :version_of :Ethernet"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :BASEF :version_of :Ethernet"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :BASEF :version_of :Ethernet"},{"questionBody":"IsBit_Torrent :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bit_Torrent :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Bit_Torrent :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Bit_Torrent :offers :Transmission_Control_Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsMicrowave :types_of :Wireless ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Microwave :types_of :Wireless"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Microwave :types_of :Wireless"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Microwave :types_of :Wireless"},{"questionBody":"IsSVOIP :extension_of :VOIP ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SVOIP :extension_of :VOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SVOIP :extension_of :VOIP"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SVOIP :extension_of :VOIP"},{"questionBody":"IsAnalog_Modulation :transmits :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Analog_Modulation :transmits :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Analog_Modulation :transmits :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Analog_Modulation :transmits :Radio_and_Spread_Spectrum"},{"questionBody":"IsARP_Poisoning :functions :Active_Attacks ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ARP_Poisoning :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ARP_Poisoning :functions :Active_Attacks"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ARP_Poisoning :functions :Active_Attacks"},{"questionBody":"IsActive_Attacks :need :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Active_Attacks :need :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsShielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Shielded_Twisted_Pair :types_of :Twisted_Pair"},{"questionBody":"IsSCP :kind_of :SSH ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SCP :kind_of :SSH"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SCP :kind_of :SSH"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SCP :kind_of :SSH"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :made_of :Management_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Management_Plane"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :utilize :Packet_Switching ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :utilize :Packet_Switching"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :provides :CBR ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :CBR"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :provides :VBR-RT ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :provides :VBR-RT"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :made_of :User_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :User_Plane"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :made_of :Control_Plane ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :made_of :Control_Plane"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :transmits :Data ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Data"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :transmits :Cells ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Cells"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :transmits :Video ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Video"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :kind_of :Protocol ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :kind_of :Protocol"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :transmits :Voice ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :transmits :Voice"},{"questionBody":"IsATM :uses :Virtual_Path ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM :uses :Virtual_Path"},{"questionBody":"IsCryptography :provides :Security ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cryptography :provides :Security"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Cryptography :provides :Security"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Cryptography :provides :Security"},{"questionBody":"IsHardline :types_of :Coaxial_Cable ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hardline :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :Hardline :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :Hardline :types_of :Coaxial_Cable"},{"questionBody":"IsSM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :SM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :SM :perfoms :Analog_Modulation"},{"questionBody":"IsATM_Layer :layer_of :ATM ?","questionType":"trueAndfalse","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Yes","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM_Layer :layer_of :ATM"},{"id":0,"text":"No","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why No is the incorrect answer is due to the following :ATM_Layer :layer_of :ATM"}],"strategy":"Terminology","bloomLvl":"Knowladge","keyFeedback":"The reason why Yes is the correct answer is due to the following :ATM_Layer :layer_of :ATM"},{"questionBody":"How many number_of_layers is IP_Suite connected with ?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"4","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"8","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 8 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 8 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"12","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 12 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 12 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"id":0,"text":"16","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why 16 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : 16 is multiplies the number_of_layers of IP_Suite and number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"}],"strategy":"Datatype-property-based","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why 4 is the correct answer is due to the following : The number_of_layers of IP_Suite is 4"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Bandwidth?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with superclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why bw is the correct answer is due to the following :bw is Bandwidth"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Computer_Networks?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks"},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the incorrect answer is due to the following : scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the incorrect answer is due to the following : sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p2 is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why perfo is the incorrect answer is due to the following : perfo is Performance"},{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why p3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : p3 is Performance"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why n1 is the correct answer is due to the following :n1 is Computer_Networks"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Security?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security"},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why interrr is the incorrect answer is due to the following : interrr is Interruption"},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why integ is the incorrect answer is due to the following : integ is Integrity"},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why confid is the incorrect answer is due to the following : confid is Confidentiality"},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why modi is the incorrect answer is due to the following : modi is Modification"},{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why availabilty is the incorrect answer is due to the following : availabilty is Availablity"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why sec is the correct answer is due to the following :sec is Security"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Scope?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"},{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s1 is Extranet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with subclasses","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why scope is the correct answer is due to the following :scope is Scope"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following examples demonstrates the concept Extranet?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s4 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s4 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s3 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s3 is Intranet"},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why s2 is the incorrect answer is due to the following : s2 is Internet"}],"strategy":"Class-Based with disjoint sibling classes","bloomLvl":"Application","keyFeedback":"The reason why s1 is the correct answer is due to the following :s1 is Extranet"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following ia a function of the Bridge?","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Translation_Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Modem","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Modem is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Modem doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Router","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Router is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Router doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"id":0,"text":"Switch","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switch is the incorrect answer is due to the following : Switch doesn't classify_as Translation_Bridge"}],"strategy":"Object-property-based","bloomLvl":"Comprehension","keyFeedback":"The reason why Translation_Bridge is the correct answer is due to the following : Translation_Bridge classify_as Translation_Bridge"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Open Systems Interconnection","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why OSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model Open Systems InterconnectionOSI_Model"},{"id":0,"text":"Flooders","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Flooders is incorrect answer is due to the following: Flooders  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Star_Mesh is incorrect answer is due to the following: Star_Mesh  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Loaded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Loaded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IP_Suite is incorrect answer is due to the following: IP_Suite  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bonded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bonded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Infrared is incorrect answer is due to the following: Infrared  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Scope is incorrect answer is due to the following: Scope  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SVOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SVOIP  is Secure Voice over IP"},{"id":0,"text":"Switched","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Switched is incorrect answer is due to the following: Switched  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why ATM_Layer is incorrect answer is due to the following: ATM_Layer  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyOSI_Model is correct answer is due to the following: OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــRemote Desktop Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDPRemote Desktop ProtocolRDP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: LDAP  is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRDP is correct answer is due to the following: RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCPMedia Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)MGCP"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: CMAC  is Cipher-based message authentication code"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyMGCP is correct answer is due to the following: MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Network Management Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMPSimple Network Management ProtocolSNMP"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SFTP  is SSH File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySNMP is correct answer is due to the following: SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Object Access Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAPSimple Object Access ProtocolSOAP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySOAP is correct answer is due to the following: SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــdirect sequence spread spectrum","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is correct answer is due to the following: DSSSdirect sequence spread spectrumDSSS"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDSSS is correct answer is due to the following: DSSS is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Real Time Streaming Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is correct answer is due to the following: RTSP Real Time Streaming ProtocolRTSP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"TLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: TLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRTSP is correct answer is due to the following: RTSP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــFile Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is correct answer is due to the following: FTPFile Transfer ProtocolFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFTP is correct answer is due to the following: FTP is File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــVoice over Internet Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is correct answer is due to the following: VOIPVoice over Internet ProtocolVOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: VOIP is Voice over Internet Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Building Automation and Control Networks","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BACnet","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why BACnet is correct answer is due to the following: BACnet Building Automation and Control NetworksBACnet"},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Ethernet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Ethernet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Internet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Internet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Internet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Telnet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Telnet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Telnet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Intranet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Intranet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Intranet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bandwidth","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bandwidth is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bandwidth  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Brouter is incorrect answer is due to the following: Brouter  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Permanent is incorrect answer is due to the following: Permanent  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Honeypots is incorrect answer is due to the following: Honeypots  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Bonded_TP is incorrect answer is due to the following: Bonded_TP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Extranet is incorrect answer is due to the following: Extranet  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Integrity","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Integrity is incorrect answer is due to the following: Integrity  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Gnutella","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Gnutella is incorrect answer is due to the following: Gnutella  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyBACnet is correct answer is due to the following: BACnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــHypertext Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HTTP is correct answer is due to the following: HTTPHypertext Transfer ProtocolHTTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHTTP is correct answer is due to the following: HTTP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSSH File Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is correct answer is due to the following: SFTPSSH File Transfer ProtocolSFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySFTP is correct answer is due to the following: SFTP is SSH File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Description Protocol (SDP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is correct answer is due to the following: SDPSession Description Protocol (SDP)SDP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySDP is correct answer is due to the following: SDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــfrequency hopping spread spectrum","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is correct answer is due to the following: FHSSfrequency hopping spread spectrumFHSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"NFS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why NFS is incorrect answer is due to the following: NFS  is Network File System"},{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSH  is Secure Shell"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFHSS is correct answer is due to the following: FHSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetwork News Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NNTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NNTPNetwork News Transfer ProtocolNNTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NNTP is Network News Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــdenial-of-service attack","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DOS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DOS is correct answer is due to the following: DOSdenial-of-service attackDOS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"DNS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DNS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DNS  is Domain Name System"},{"id":0,"text":"DTLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DTLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DTLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDOS is correct answer is due to the following: DOS is denial-of-service attack"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSimple Mail Transfer Protocol ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is correct answer is due to the following: SMTPSimple Mail Transfer Protocol SMTP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySMTP is correct answer is due to the following: SMTP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ARPANET","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why ARPANET is correct answer is due to the following: ARPANET Advanced Research Projects Agency NetworkARPANET"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASETX","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASETX is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASETX  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET4","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET4 is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET4  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"BASET2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why BASET2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: BASET2  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyARPANET is correct answer is due to the following: ARPANET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDomain Name System","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DNS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DNS is correct answer is due to the following: DNSDomain Name SystemDNS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"DOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DOS  is denial-of-service attack"},{"id":0,"text":"DTLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DTLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DTLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDNS is correct answer is due to the following: DNS is Domain Name System"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Engineering Task Force","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is correct answer is due to the following: IETFInternet Engineering Task ForceIETF"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is incorrect answer is due to the following: IPTV  is Internet Protocol television"},{"id":0,"text":"DICT","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DICT is incorrect answer is due to the following: DICT  is Dictionary Server Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIETF is correct answer is due to the following: IETF is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSynchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SDH is correct answer is due to the following: SDHSynchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)SDH"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDM  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySDH is correct answer is due to the following: SDH is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــLightweight Directory Access Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is correct answer is due to the following: LDAPLightweight Directory Access ProtocolLDAP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDP  is Session Description Protocol (SDP)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyLDAP is correct answer is due to the following: LDAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Assigned Numbers Authority","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is correct answer is due to the following: IANAInternet Assigned Numbers AuthorityIANA"},{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAB  is Internet Architecture Board"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIANA is correct answer is due to the following: IANA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Point to Point Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why PPP is correct answer is due to the following: PPP Point to Point ProtocolPPP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"POP1","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP1 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP1  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyPPP is correct answer is due to the following: PPP is  Point to Point Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSecure Shell","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is correct answer is due to the following: SSHSecure ShellSSH"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SDH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SDH  is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySSH is correct answer is due to the following: SSH is Secure Shell"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــPost Office Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why POP is correct answer is due to the following: POPPost Office ProtocolPOP"},{"id":0,"text":"POP2","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why POP2 is incorrect answer is due to the following: POP2  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyPOP is correct answer is due to the following: POP is Post Office Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDynamic Host Configuration Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is correct answer is due to the following: DHCPDynamic Host Configuration ProtocolDHCP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"PHP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PHP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PHP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDHCP is correct answer is due to the following: DHCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Architecture Board","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is correct answer is due to the following: IABInternet Architecture BoardIAB"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IAX","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAX is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAX  is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIAB is correct answer is due to the following: IAB is Internet Architecture Board"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ chirp spread spectrum ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why CSS is correct answer is due to the following: CSS chirp spread spectrum CSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FHSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: FHSS  is frequency hopping spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyCSS is correct answer is due to the following: CSS is  chirp spread spectrum "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــServer Message Block","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SMB is correct answer is due to the following: SMBServer Message BlockSMB"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"SSB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSB is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSB  is single sideband modulation"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySMB is correct answer is due to the following: SMB is Server Message Block"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Protocol television","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is correct answer is due to the following: IPTVInternet Protocol televisionIPTV"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why PPTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: PPTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIPTV is correct answer is due to the following: IPTV is Internet Protocol television"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــHyperText Markup Language","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTML","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HTML is correct answer is due to the following: HTMLHyperText Markup LanguageHTML"},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HTTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: HTTP  is Hypertext Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"TDM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TDM is incorrect answer is due to the following: TDM  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHTML is correct answer is due to the following: HTML is HyperText Markup Language"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــ Network Basic Input Output System","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NetBIOS is correct answer is due to the following: NetBIOS Network Basic Input Output SystemNetBIOS"},{"id":0,"text":"Direct_DS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Direct_DS is incorrect answer is due to the following: Direct_DS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Network","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Network is incorrect answer is due to the following: Network  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why JUNOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: JUNOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why ZyNOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: ZyNOS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNetBIOS is correct answer is due to the following: NetBIOS is  Network Basic Input Output System"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــDictionary Server Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DICT","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why DICT is correct answer is due to the following: DICTDictionary Server ProtocolDICT"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyDICT is correct answer is due to the following: DICT is Dictionary Server Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــQuadrature amplitude modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"QAM","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why QAM is correct answer is due to the following: QAMQuadrature amplitude modulationQAM"},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: CMAC  is Cipher-based message authentication code"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HMAC is incorrect answer is due to the following: HMAC  is hash message authentication code"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyQAM is correct answer is due to the following: QAM is Quadrature amplitude modulation"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــCipher-based message authentication code","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CMAC","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why CMAC is correct answer is due to the following: CMACCipher-based message authentication codeCMAC"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"QAM","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why QAM is incorrect answer is due to the following: QAM  is Quadrature amplitude modulation"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyCMAC is correct answer is due to the following: CMAC is Cipher-based message authentication code"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet Research Task Force","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IRTF","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IRTF is correct answer is due to the following: IRTFInternet Research Task ForceIRTF"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IETF","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IETF is incorrect answer is due to the following: IETF  is Internet Engineering Task Force"},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IPTV is incorrect answer is due to the following: IPTV  is Internet Protocol television"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIRTF is correct answer is due to the following: IRTF is Internet Research Task Force"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_A","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_A is correct answer is due to the following: Class_AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaClass_A"},{"id":0,"text":"Wireless","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Wireless is incorrect answer is due to the following: Wireless  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_E","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_E is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_E  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Star_Mesh is incorrect answer is due to the following: Star_Mesh  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_Fa","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_Fa is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_Fa  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_D","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_D is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_D  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_C","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_C is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_C  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_F is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_F  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Cells","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Cells is incorrect answer is due to the following: Cells  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Plastics","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Plastics is incorrect answer is due to the following: Plastics  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"Class_B","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why Class_B is incorrect answer is due to the following: Class_B  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyClass_A is correct answer is due to the following: Class_A is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــRouting Information Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RIP is correct answer is due to the following: RIPRouting Information ProtocolRIP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: VOIP  is Voice over Internet Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRIP is correct answer is due to the following: RIP is Routing Information Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Initiation Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SIP is correct answer is due to the following: SIPSession Initiation ProtocolSIP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why VOIP is incorrect answer is due to the following: VOIP  is Voice over Internet Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySIP is correct answer is due to the following: SIP is Session Initiation Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــMultipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MIME","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why MIME is correct answer is due to the following: MIMEMultipurpose Internet Mail ExtensionsMIME"},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IDEA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IDEA  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"MPPE","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MPPE is incorrect answer is due to the following: MPPE  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyMIME is correct answer is due to the following: MIME is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــTime hopping spread spectrum ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"THSS","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why THSS is correct answer is due to the following: THSSTime hopping spread spectrum THSS"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"TLS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why TLS is incorrect answer is due to the following: TLS  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyTHSS is correct answer is due to the following: THSS is Time hopping spread spectrum "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــFiber to the x","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTX","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTX is correct answer is due to the following: FTTXFiber to the xFTTX"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyFTTX is correct answer is due to the following: FTTX is Fiber to the x"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــTrivial File Transfer Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TFTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why TFTP is correct answer is due to the following: TFTPTrivial File Transfer ProtocolTFTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTC is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTC  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyTFTP is correct answer is due to the following: TFTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInternet message access protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is correct answer is due to the following: IMAPInternet message access protocolIMAP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIMAP is correct answer is due to the following: IMAP is Internet message access protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSession Traversal Utilities for NAT","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STUN","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why STUN is correct answer is due to the following: STUNSession Traversal Utilities for NATSTUN"},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTTN is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTTN  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SFTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SFTP  is SSH File Transfer Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySTUN is correct answer is due to the following: STUN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــActive Server Pages","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ASP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why ASP is correct answer is due to the following: ASPActive Server PagesASP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyASP is correct answer is due to the following: ASP is Active Server Pages"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــsingle sideband modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSB","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SSB is correct answer is due to the following: SSBsingle sideband modulationSSB"},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DSSS is incorrect answer is due to the following: DSSS  is direct sequence spread spectrum"},{"id":0,"text":"SSH","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSH is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSH  is Secure Shell"},{"id":0,"text":"SSTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SSTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SSTP  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySSB is correct answer is due to the following: SSB is single sideband modulation"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــwireless local area network","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"WLAN","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why WLAN is correct answer is due to the following: WLANwireless local area networkWLAN"},{"id":0,"text":"AAL","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why AAL is incorrect answer is due to the following: AAL  is ATM Adaptation Layer"},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why LDAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: LDAP  is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyWLAN is correct answer is due to the following: WLAN is wireless local area network"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــhash message authentication code","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HMAC","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why HMAC is correct answer is due to the following: HMAChash message authentication codeHMAC"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why DHCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: DHCP  is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"HTML","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why HTML is incorrect answer is due to the following: HTML  is HyperText Markup Language"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyHMAC is correct answer is due to the following: HMAC is hash message authentication code"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــInter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why IAX is correct answer is due to the following: IAXInter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)IAX"},{"id":0,"text":"IANA","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IANA is incorrect answer is due to the following: IANA  is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority"},{"id":0,"text":"IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IAB is incorrect answer is due to the following: IAB  is Internet Architecture Board"},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IMAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: IMAP  is Internet message access protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyIAX is correct answer is due to the following: IAX is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــJavaServer Pages","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"JSP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why JSP is correct answer is due to the following: JSPJavaServer PagesJSP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SOAP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SOAP  is Simple Object Access Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyJSP is correct answer is due to the following: JSP is JavaServer Pages"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetWare Core Protocol","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NCP is correct answer is due to the following: NCPNetWare Core ProtocolNCP"},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why MGCP is incorrect answer is due to the following: MGCP  is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"NNTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why NNTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: NNTP  is Network News Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNCP is correct answer is due to the following: NCP is NetWare Core Protocol"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــReal-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why RTP is correct answer is due to the following: RTPReal-time Transport Protocol (RTP)RTP"},{"id":0,"text":"RDP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RDP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RDP  is Remote Desktop Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyRTP is correct answer is due to the following: RTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــNetwork Time Protocol ","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why NTP is correct answer is due to the following: NTPNetwork Time Protocol NTP"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why RTSP is incorrect answer is due to the following: RTSP  is  Real Time Streaming Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why FTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: FTP  is File Transfer Protocol"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whyNTP is correct answer is due to the following: NTP is Network Time Protocol "},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــSecure Voice over IP","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: SVOIPSecure Voice over IPSVOIP"},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why OSI_Model is incorrect answer is due to the following: OSI_Model  is  Open Systems Interconnection"},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why CISCO_IOS is incorrect answer is due to the following: CISCO_IOS  is null"},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why IP_Suite is incorrect answer is due to the following: IP_Suite  is null"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySVOIP is correct answer is due to the following: SVOIP is Secure Voice over IP"},{"questionBody":"Analyse the following text and decide which one of the following words is a correct replacement for the blank space in the text: ’A ــــــــــــــــspace modulation","questionType":null,"choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SM","isCorrectAnswer":true,"feedBack":"The reason why SM is correct answer is due to the following: SMspace modulationSM"},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SNMP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SNMP  is Simple Network Management Protocol"},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMTP is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMTP  is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol "},{"id":0,"text":"SMB","isCorrectAnswer":false,"feedBack":"The reason why SMB is incorrect answer is due to the following: SMB  is Server Message Block"}],"strategy":"property","bloomLvl":null,"keyFeedback":"The reason whySM is correct answer is due to the following: SM is space modulation"}]